discretesearch.com 2019-08-06

# Privacy Policy

## Welcome to the Discrete Search Privacy Policy

Discrete Search (“we” or “us”) respects and protects the privacy of consumers; and is committed to delivering a privacy-safe search environment. When you use Discrete Search, you trust us with your searches and we understand and value this trust. We have provided this Privacy Policy to explain how Discrete Search protects your privacy while searching, what information we collect through Discrete Search and some of your privacy rights regarding that information. 

Effective April, 2019

### **Summary of our Discrete Search Practices**

1\. Discrete Search does not track search history in any user identifiable way. 

The most popular search engines create search profiles of specific users in order to retarget ads based on those search queries as the user navigates the internet. Discrete Search does not track your search history in any user identifiable way. 

2\. Discrete Search does not retain server logs.

Discrete Search does not use tracking tool or maintain logs that compromise your privacy. 

3\. Discrete Search prevents your ISP from tracking your search terms.

Some search engines do not encrypt your queries, which means your Internet Service Provider (ISP) can intercept and access them and connect them to your web and/or cable account. When you use Discrete Search, your search queries are encrypted so that your ISP cannot read them.

4\. Discrete Search does not associate your searches from your online accounts.

The most popular search engines offer other services which often collect sensitive personal information such as email (Gmail, Outlook Webmail, and Yahoo! Mail) and social web services (Google+ and YouTube). When you search the web and remain logged into these accounts, your search queries can be easily connected to your profile.

Discrete Search completely disconnects your searches from being tied to your email accounts and social profiles.

5\. Discrete Search helps hide your search history on your device.

Discrete Search uses proprietary technology to hide you search history from others who may use your device after you search. This may save you from some embarrassing situations.

6\. More Information.

For more information about protecting your privacy, you may wish to visit http://www.netcoalition.com and http://www.privacyalliance.org. If you wish to be notified of any updates to this Privacy Policy, please check back frequently as any updates will be posted to DiscreteSearch.com with a new effective date.

### **Information We May Collect**

To the extent you have not altered the default settings of the Discrete Search product, we do not use cookies. If you have altered such default settings, we will utilize cookies to store your preferred settings, but the information stored is not personally identifiable. 

Additionally, we store aggregated search data to improve product performance, but never store IP addresses or unique user identifiers in connection with such searches in order to ensure that none of the information collected in connection with your search activity is personally identifiable. 

In some circumstances, we may append an affiliate code to certain sites linked to our Discrete Search product, either directly or through search results delivered to you. In doing so, we may collect a small commission in connection with your activity, but do not pass any of your personally identifiable information to any such third party sites. We do not utilize any third party to assist us with appending such affiliate code and we do not work with any third party site that collects personally identifiable information in connection with our participation in such affiliate programs. As such, no personally identifiable information is shared from our Discrete Search product and the only information that is collected is product information that is not relatable to any particular end user and we do not retain such information in any case. 

To the extent you provide us with feedback, we may store your email address if you provide it (but you are not required to do so). 

###  **Information We May Share**

As noted above, unless you alter the default settings of the Discrete Search product, we do not share personally identifiable information about you to any third party. In circumstances where you have chosen to alter the default settings, then your personally identifiable information may be shared with third party site operators. 

To the extent we receive any legally binding request to comply with a court order or applicable law, we will share the information requested of us to the extent we have it, but, as noted above, we would expect this information to be very limited and likely of little use given our default settings. 

###  **This Policy may change from time to time. Please check back frequently for updates.**

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy and your rights under this policy, please write to us at the address below.
